bloodlinechampions.com 2012-05-22

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Stunlock Studios AB provides this Privacy Statement to inform you of our privacy policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. ****

**Purpose of Policy  
**This policy is made to make sure that you know and feel confident in how we handle the personal information you provide us with.

**All information collected through this webpage and the game Bloodline Champions is property of Stunlock Studios AB**

We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any third parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

We do not knowingly collect data from anyone under the age of 13.

**Cookies  
**Our site may use cookies, a cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the users and how she uses the website. Cookies are used to give you a more pleasent way to use our webservices and to give us information on how we can improve our service. If you choose not to allow cookies in your browser, some of the features on our site might not work properly.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (ex. Banners). We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**Log Files**

We may use IP addresses to gather anonymous "traffic data" to analyze user behavior. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use this information for marketing purposes and/or for improving the services we offer to you. 

**Anonymous Information  
**We use anonymous information to analyze user behavior and for marketing research. We may share information that can't identify any individual person with our partners and advertisers. 

**Personal Information**  
We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide you with the services offered by us or to comply with the law. 

**Disclosure of Personal Information  
**We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law. 

We may have partners that help us provide specific services to you. We may share your personal information with them so they can provide these services to you. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

**Forums and chatrooms**  
As a user you agree to any information you have entered to being stored in a database. While personal information will not be disclosed to any third party without your consent, we may share information that is not personally identifiable with third parties to analyze user behavior. Any information you share on the forums and chat rooms are public information. That information may be read by everyone who uses those services, so please exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Third-party sites and links**  
Our site may contain links to other websites, these websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy and we are not responsible for any content found on those sites.

**Access to information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes, or if a user wish to have her personal information removed from our database, we will provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data from our databas. 

**Change of policy  
**We reserve the right to change and modify this policy at any time, these changes and modifications will be posted on our site to make sure you know how your information is handled. Any changed will be effective immediately when posted on our Site. If you don't accept the changes we make to the policy you should make sure your information is removed by us and your use of the service we provide should end.
